<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nice Website</title>
    <description>Some description about this nice website.</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 06:08:55 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 06:08:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;


      &lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
          &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;

            &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
              &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Advanced UX&lt;/h1&gt;

              &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;I work in the design studio at &lt;b&gt;Mercedes-Benz R&amp;amp;D North America&lt;/b&gt;.  We focus on innovations such as fuelcell, self-driving, 3d graphics, and advanced design.



                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; My focus within the studio covers speech interaction and natural language processing. Of course I&#39;m under a NDA, so I can&#39;t share with you the actual work, so instead I&#39;ll highlight the process and problems surrounding my AI project.  &lt;/p&gt;


                &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Designing intelligence&lt;/h1&gt;
                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                Most people I&#39;ve talked to are not sold on the value of siri, alexa, and similar natural language voice interfaces. Some interfaces may disappoint users by sounding smarter than they really are, but what people really mean to say is that the voice interface isn&#39;t smart enough. &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                At first, that may seem like an easy problem to grasp. Smart design means putting the user first, meaning.. (1) start with a need (2) design an intuitive layout, (3) provide interactive content, (4) optimize by testing &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                Unfortunately, this isn&#39;t the case. &lt;b&gt;When designing for intelligence, simple is not better&lt;/b&gt;. The goal is to make the interface replicate the thought process of a human - not a puppet you can pinch and drag like clickbait. Part of the &quot;magic&quot; is delightfully surprising the user. The point is to avoid explicit visuals and overt commands. I&#39;m really excited about this shift because it&#39;s a chance for us ourselves to become smarter and more human because of the technology we interact with. &lt;p&gt;

                
                &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Natural language processing&lt;/h1&gt;
                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                So how do you replicate the intelligence of a human? In my case, it&#39;s through a voice agent. So I&#39;ve been working on how the agent understands what you&#39;re saying as well as how it should talk back. Here are a few problems I&#39;ve spent my time solving:
                &lt;p&gt;

                
               


                &lt;ul&gt;
                  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt; How do you dynamically create and update non-verbal context in voice interaction?&lt;/b&gt;

                  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt; Teaching an agent to extract a combination of names, titles, and descriptions referenced in a single utterance&lt;/b&gt;

                  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt; Taking an indirect reference made by the user and assigning it to an object with the help of prepositions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt; 

                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt; Sometimes it&#39;s still better to show then tell, so how do you anthropomorphize a GUI without being creepy? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;  





                
                &lt;p&gt;


               &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Moving fast means cutting corners&lt;/h1&gt;
               &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;   
               On one hand, I had to find (scalable) ways to map out, compromise, then phrase these linguistic rules into functional statements. On the other hand, users don&#39;t always follow all of these grammatical rules to begin with. So generally speaking, my solution combined outlining basic linguistic conventions with training through user input. Because my focus was designing interactions, it didn&#39;t make sense to feed the machine large amounts of data for marginal improvements and extreme wildcards. For the loose ends, it was more practical to tape it together with scripts.
               &lt;p&gt;

               &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
               On the UX end, I avoided personas. Part of the beauty with language, after all, is that it&#39;s universal so we have widely shared conventions of speech. All I had to do was stop thinking and start talking. My first example dialogues were me pretending to speak to my mother. Although some designers recommend speaking to the agent like you&#39;re asking a stranger a question, my goal was to design a smarter agent; one where you could say less white it understands more - just like your mother. After this initial stage, I broadened my syntax and incrementally made myself harder to understand. 
               At the same time, I started designing and developing the GUI that I eventually hooked up to my voice interface and loaded onto the car&#39;s linux machine. The nice thing about cars is that people are in a nice private space that is acoustically absorbent. As you might know, people are more comfortable speaking and singing out loud when in a car. 
               &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;p class=&quot;lead-center&quot;&gt; 
                &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/mercedes/meme.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt; relevant meme &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Takeaways&lt;/h1&gt;
                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                As UX designers, we&#39;re practical problem solvers. For us it&#39;s more about the functionality; there&#39;s no such thing as a proper way. You can&#39;t really &quot;fake&quot; a natural language demo, but there are still more and less practical ways of achieving your goal. What I learned in the process was that &lt;i&gt; even though &lt;/i&gt; we have these new techniques like deep learning at our hands, the agent/program doesn&#39;t have to think the same way a human does in order to present itself like it thinks the same way a human does.
                &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                There&#39;s nothing wrong with artificial intelligence being artificial. And we ourselves rely on this phenomenon all the time - like when you interview, or when your when someone asks you for advice (kidding). Realizing this was a milestone in my jedi journey as a designer that codes (basically coding = the dark side; solving abstract problems becomes tempting as your powers grow but designers maintain order by using our judgement aka the force to create things people actually care about).
                &lt;p&gt; 

                &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Related projects&lt;/h1&gt;
                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                Each year some work from our studio is shown publicly at CES. If you want to get a better idea of how intelligent interaction plays into cars, check out these projects my team has worked on in the past. Just to be clear, I was not involved in either of these past projects.
                &lt;p&gt;

                  &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;2015 F 015&lt;/h1&gt;
                  
                  &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/GAz42C5Vvt8&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                   &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;2016 concept IAA&lt;/h1&gt;
                 
                  &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fBwmH7TAupI&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;


           
              
            
          
        
      
    
  

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Mercedes/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Mercedes/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Airquail</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
        
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;AirQuail&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Airquail is the internet of things hardware startup that I cofounded. It started as a weekend hackathon project that turned into a fulltime pursuit after we joined Hackcelerator, a 12 week accelerator program during the summer. We&#39;re currently on our 3rd hardware prototype and have our devices in local school districts for testing purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

        Just a disclaimer, i might be talking more about business problems than issues purely with product design.

        Our time and resources are limited, so we made some tough decisions on which combinations of gases we wanted to monitor. Early on, when making decisions about the product, it&#39;s not always about the customer, the market, or what&#39;s usable. If we were going to dedicate our lives to building a product, it better be something we ourselves wanted to use. So although healthcare was a hot market, I strongly believed we should focus more on gases associated with comfort and wellness. We don&#39;t want to be an alarm that monitors that monitors that toxic gas that will kills 50 people a year, and we also didn&#39;t want to just monitor gases that will shorten your lives by 12 months. Instead, it&#39;s about telling people more about the gases that are always around you yet you can&#39;t see and how they can unconciously influence your lifestyle. So that&#39;s why we went with Carbon Dioxide, Carbon Monoxide, Pm 2.5. We also added other sensors such as temperature, humidity, pressure for the sole purpose of making our primary gas algorithims more accurate.

        Hardware design
        It had to be portable, why we selected wifi , form factor and costs $90

        Software
        We had an ios app and webapp and showed epa data blablalbalbalal

        Finding partnerships
        How we found chiense company

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;The team&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  &lt;/p&gt; 


        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Hardware&lt;/h1&gt;


        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/h1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/h2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/h3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        

        
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;The Webapp&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p&gt; first webapp &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/app3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        &lt;p&gt; most recent webapp &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/DemoDesktop.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Readings taken from our device&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/ss1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/ss2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/ss3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Demo Day&lt;/h1&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; After our 12 week accelerator I presented our progress at demo day. You can check out the video here. &lt;/p&gt;



      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/AirQuail/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/AirQuail/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Fedup&lt;/h1&gt;



        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;It&#39;s crazy that in the 21st century law enforcement/legal system still rely heavily on foggy testimony and paper police reports. So we built a complete ecosystem for users to directly document, review and share evidence without having to go through anyone else. &lt;/p&gt;

         &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
          &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xdvQbL0FFj8&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
         &lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Design considerations&lt;/h1&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Visually, the goal was to make the android app look like a badge worn by an officer - it goes along with our mission making citizens feel more empowered. &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/fedup/a1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;



        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  At the same time, we wanted to protect user privacy and allow them to run the app from their pocket. For this reason, we went recording audio instead of recording Video. Video would have also made our technology less usable in conditions with poor lighting.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Unlike our android app, the web component carried a lighter layout intended for use on the desktop. Whether it&#39;s the victim organizing an account the day after, lawyers browsing client folders, or public viewers browsing fact-oriented stories, the key was to deisgn a pleasant layout that supports a wide variety of media without dumbing content down. &lt;p&gt;




          &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Update&lt;/h1&gt;

          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/fedup/banner.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;



          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; After deciding to continue this project, we connected with the American Civil Liberties Union and entered an official partnership with them. We also connected with the Harvard Law&#39;s Berkman Center. The goal of working with these larger organizations was gain access to more data for our web component.&lt;/p&gt;

        

      
    
  
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2007 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Fed-Up/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Fed-Up/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Chimehack 2&lt;/h1&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;Over the summer, I went to Chimehack2 with a few friends. It&#39;s a hackathon hosted by twitter to promote hacking for change.&lt;/p&gt;

      




      &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Making College a Safer Space&lt;/h1&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; One of the categories for Chimehack was campus safety. To brainstorm, we thought back on our experiences with campus safety. Usually when your friend goes missing, they&#39;re not picking up their phone and you don&#39;t know whether or not their phone is dead. They&#39;re probably not in enough danger to call campus safety, but that doesn&#39;t mean you&#39;re not concerned for your friend. &lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; That&#39;s why we built an iOS app called asOne. It&#39;s a better way to communicate in groups when going out. Instead of annoying group messages, we create temporary friend groups that shares information about each member&#39;s location, battery level, and the time they want to go home. &lt;/p&gt;


      &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;The Design Process&lt;/h1&gt;   

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Because we had 48 hours to build everything, I had about 12 hours to work through the user flow and freeze visual design. We formed teams friday night. I spent the next morning designing and going through tough choices with my teamates. A little after lunch, I was ready to export the assets. &lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/asone/asonef.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Usability was my key concern, so I spent a large chunk of my time refining the onboarding process. Because we were at twitter, we receieved a lot of feedback about the challenges when creating a product that only works  when many users choose to engage. They just started promoting Periscope at the time, and even for such an established company, we learned that there&#39;s really no way of knowig the success until it&#39;s out there.



        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Here&#39;s a screenshot of the splash screen, illustrating the brand and styling.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/asone/a6.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; One goal of Chimehack 2 was to promote inclusivness in technology. Likewise, the goal of our app was to make it easier for friend groups to stay together when out on a weekend. A key theme throughout the weekend was inclusiveness, so stylistically I wanted to convey friendliness and draw a diverse user base. To convey friendliess I went with warm passionate blends and a heart shaped logo. The best thing I could do to make sure we didn&#39;t attract the traditional tech-y user base was to make the app look less stereotypical, hence the granjon/roman typeface that you may recognise when walking around a mall...&lt;/p&gt;   


        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; The resting screen&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/asone/a1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  We used the facebook SDK when generating user accounts so our avators are pulled from our profiles. Key features include

          - displaying distance from friend based on location info
          - displaying battery life


          As well as user friendly conviniences such as

          - predefined status updates 
          - push notifications for entire group

          You can&#39;t see our our friend Revan&#39;s battery status because he has an adroid and we built this for iOS. We&#39;re all the same distance apart because we were standing next to eachother.


        &lt;/p&gt;   


        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; The detail screen.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/asone/a5.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Usually when you&#39;ve assembled your group, there&#39;s one person missing. When calling doesn&#39;t work, we have an inline map that points you in the direction of that person. &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/asone.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;   


        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; We built this app because this was a tool missing from our everyday lives, and for the rest of the summer we would often use it as a tool to ping and find eachother. Since then, Apple released a standalone friend finder, and we also saw an app named Companion gain popularity around college campuses. &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; In restrospect, the technology wasn&#39;t earth shattering, but this is a great example of how fast a talented team can work when there is good chemistry. In one weekend, we shipped a product that would take a company at least half a year to assemble.&lt;/p&gt;

        
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;More about Chimehack&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
        &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/86ECVBcPWcg&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
        

        
      
    
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2006 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/As-One/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/As-One/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Benzpay</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; &lt;/h1&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; This is the winning hackathon project that caught the attention of Daimler&#39;s board members. We had the chance to meet Dr. Z as well as all the other executives during their yearly meeting. They were extremely impressed, and subsequently what lead me to a job at Mercedes.  &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; The idea &lt;/h1&gt;

         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; The idea is that mobile payment is all around us. It&#39;s made our lives easier and more secure. Yet when leaving a parking garage or stopping at a toll booth, for some reason we&#39;re still wasting time fumbling for money or trying to stick a card in a machine. That&#39;s why we created BenzPay, because for the Mercedes driver, time is the only currency that matters.  &lt;/p&gt;

          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/benzpay.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

         &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Simplifying the use case &lt;/h1&gt;
         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; We didn&#39;t have much time to do our demo so I narrowed down the use cases to the three most important to a driver. Gas and parking are hands down the most important, but the final use case was much harder to choose. &lt;p&gt;

          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/a3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
          I eventually went with events instead of toll booths for a couple reasons:

          &lt;ol type=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;There are already existing payment sollutions for tollbooths. &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;We wanted to appeal to an emotional side of our product. It&#39;s one thing to make your life easier, it&#39;s another to make it more interesting.  &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Quick to implement, completing transactions on ticketmaster or eventbrite requires no additional hardware unlike support for parking meters, gas pumps, or toll booths. &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;/ol&gt;
           &lt;/p&gt;


       

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/a4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;


          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
            Other features include using gps and bitcoin to complete transactions without the need to stop, or by automatically calculating and paying for the price to fill up at a given gas station.
            &lt;p&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Designing on car interfaces &lt;/h1&gt;     

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  
        Designing applications for the car is a little different than designing applications for the phone or the web. Unless the driver is parked, most interactions occur without the user&#39;s complete attention. That&#39;s why payments are automatically triggered by location and unique pairing. Everything is automatic, and all the driver needs to do is confirm the amount alerted to the driver. Bitcoin was the easiest to integrate for our prototype but the concept to support other payments is the same.&lt;p&gt;

         &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/a6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  
        Additionaly, not all cars (including this c300) support touch input, so there must be a clear hierarchy when navigating through each menu.
        &lt;p&gt;

       

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/a5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

      
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  
        Ensuring readability also means it&#39;s an interface easy to glance over.  This is an image of the payment history view. Only the most relevant information is made visible, and thus the bitcoin address is barely visible. 
        &lt;p&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Demo video &lt;/h1&gt;   

           &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/132971331&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

         


      
    
  

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/BenzPay/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/BenzPay/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left &quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Wifi Beerbong&lt;/h1&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;Purely for fun project, no explaination needed. Built with particle.io, firebase, node, react. Basically the beer bong contains a flow sensor and a battery powered wifi arduino. When beer is chugged, we send a a post request with a timestamp over to our webapp. Webapp consists of leaderboard, user Id&#39;s done by facebook sdk.  &lt;p&gt;

  &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/drankadank&quot;&gt; https://github.com/drankadank &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;



        
      
    
  

  &lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;row text-center&quot;&gt;
   &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;tagline&quot;&gt; 
      
         
          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
         We short circuited everything on our first test. Luckily I had a seconded particle photon with me. Made sure our enclosure was waterproof.
        &lt;/p&gt;

           &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/beerbong/a1.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Wifi-Beerbong/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Wifi-Beerbong/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
       &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;1972 Firebird&lt;/h1&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Basically, when I was a freshmen in college, I bought a muscle car with holes in the floor and worms in the seats. &lt;/p&gt;


       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; I rebuilt the motor in my dorm parking lot. Me retapping an engine block thread: &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; My hallmates complained it always smelled like gasoline &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Hey at least I didn&#39;t set the place on fire &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; I also rewired all the electronics &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; And made my own dashboard out of pine &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; I usually drive it around without the hood &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;


       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; So yeah I like cars &lt;/p&gt;

     &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2003 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Firebird/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Firebird/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Music Videos &lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Back in college, I used to work in video production and post-production. Here are a few videos from work/fun. They&#39;ve been featured on some of those hip underground sites.&lt;/p&gt;

        

            

              &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; On the steps &lt;/h1&gt;
              &lt;!-- &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; My favorite part about rappers is their work ethic - the hustle, the grind - having a dayjob and hitting the studio at night. I guess it&#39;s the same reason I love startups. It&#39;s about being young, living your dreams while everyones telling you your stupid. &lt;/p&gt; --&gt;

               &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  Visually I wanted to extend the mood of the song. The shutter speed is slow to get that smooth motion blur, and the cuts are also slow. Shot at 35mm and 50mm wide open so its tight but soft. Didn&#39;t want to overdo camera movement, so  I kept things interesting with carefully planned sequenced lighting. I preserved the beautiful characteristics and colors from dim ambient light while adding very subtle reflected accents through sources such as my warm car blinkers or my cool phone flash covered by my finger.
                &lt;/p&gt;

               &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                  &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JkA_sGRfyKA&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
               &lt;/div&gt;


              &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; SOS &lt;/h1&gt;
              &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; This one is your day in the life sort of editing structure. Most rap videos in recent years are shot on cropped sensors with tight lenses, resulting in a lot of camera shake remedied by fast cuts - it&#39;s a nice raw style. But this video looks different because many shots are of a much wider angle. The intro is way too long, and for the 10k views we got, half of them probably stopped watching it before the video even started. &lt;/p&gt;



               &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                  &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/1zxIuoUDaXA&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
               &lt;/div&gt;



               &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Salad Days &lt;/h1&gt;
              &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Pickathon is Portland&#39;s largest music festival. Like everything in Portland, it&#39;s super underground and happens in a forest.&lt;/p&gt;

               &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                  &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VoGNw78eYzc&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
               &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2002 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Music-Videos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Music-Videos/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Resume &lt;/h1&gt;


        &lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
            &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left buffer0&quot;&gt;


&lt;!--            &lt;embed class=&quot;resume&quot; src=&quot;../../images/rresume.pdf&quot; alt=&quot;pdf viewer only&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500px&quot; alt=&quot;pdf&quot; pluginspage=&quot;http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep2.html&quot;&gt; --&gt;

              &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-4by3&quot;&gt;
                  &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;../../images/rresume.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;


		
            &lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/More-Projects/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/More-Projects/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
