<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nice Website</title>
    <description>Some description about this nice website.</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 15:42:33 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 15:42:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
              &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Advanced UX&lt;/h1&gt;

              &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;I work in the design studio at &lt;b&gt;Mercedes-Benz R&amp;amp;D North America&lt;/b&gt;.  We focus on innovations such as fuelcell, self-driving, 3d graphics, and advanced design.



                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; My focus within the studio covers speech interaction and natural language processing. Of course I&#39;m under a NDA, so I can&#39;t share with you the actual work, so instead I&#39;ll highlight the process and problems surrounding my AI project.  &lt;/p&gt;


                &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Designing intelligence&lt;/h1&gt;
                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                Most people I&#39;ve talked to are not sold on the value of siri, alexa, and similar natural language voice interfaces. Some interfaces may disappoint users by sounding smarter than they really are, but what people really mean to say is that &lt;b&gt; the voice interface isn&#39;t smart enough. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                At first, that may seem like an easy problem to grasp. Smart design means putting the user first, meaning.. (1) start with a need (2) design an intuitive layout, (3) provide interactive content, (4) optimize by testing &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                Unfortunately, this isn&#39;t the case. &lt;b&gt;When designing for intelligence, simple is not better&lt;/b&gt;. The goal is to make the interface replicate the thought process of a human - not a puppet you can pinch and drag like clickbait. Part of the &quot;magic&quot; is delightfully surprising the user. The point is to avoid explicit visuals and overt commands. I&#39;m really excited about this shift because it&#39;s a chance for us ourselves to become smarter and more human because of the technology we interact with. &lt;p&gt;

                
                &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Natural language processing&lt;/h1&gt;
                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                &lt;b&gt; So how do you replicate the intelligence of a human? &lt;/b&gt; In my case, it&#39;s through a voice agent. So I&#39;ve been working on how the agent understands what you&#39;re saying as well as how it should talk back. Here are a few problems I&#39;ve spent my time solving:
                &lt;p&gt;

                
               


                &lt;ul&gt;
                  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt; How do you dynamically create and update non-verbal context  in voice interaction?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

                  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;i&gt; &lt;b&gt; Teaching an agent to extract a combination of names, titles, and descriptions referenced in a single utterance&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

                  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Taking an indirect reference made by the user and assigning it to an object with the help of prepositions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;p&gt; 

                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Sometimes it&#39;s still better to show then tell, so how do you anthropomorphize a GUI without being creepy? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;p&gt;  





                
                &lt;p&gt;


               &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Moving fast means cutting corners&lt;/h1&gt;
               &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;   
               &lt;b&gt; If there were such a thing as a linguistic rulebook, it wouldn&#39;t be worth teaching to my agent&lt;/b&gt;.  On one hand, I had to find (scalable) ways to map out, compromise, then phrase these linguistic rules into functional statements. On the other hand, users don&#39;t always follow all of these grammatical rules to begin with. So generally speaking, my solution combined outlining basic linguistic conventions with training through user input. Because my focus was designing interactions, it didn&#39;t make sense to feed the machine large amounts of data for marginal improvements and extreme wildcards. For the loose ends, it was more practical to tape it together with scripts.
               &lt;p&gt;

               &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
               &lt;b&gt; Language is more inuitive to humans than any app ever designed &lt;/b&gt;. So to put myself in the shoes of the user, all I had to do was stop thinking about how computers worked and start talking like I would to a person.. My first example dialogues were me pretending to speak to my mother. Although some designers recommend speaking to the agent like you&#39;re asking a stranger a question, my goal was to design a smarter agent; one where you could say less white it understands more - just like your mother. After this initial stage, I broadened my syntax and incrementally made myself harder to understand. 
               At the same time, I started designing and developing the GUI that I eventually hooked up to my voice interface and loaded onto the car&#39;s linux machine. The nice thing about cars is that people are in a nice private space that is acoustically absorbent. As you might know, people are more comfortable speaking and singing out loud when in a car. 
               &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;p class=&quot;lead-center&quot;&gt; 
                &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/mercedes/meme.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt; * relevant design meme *&lt;p&gt;

                &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Takeaways&lt;/h1&gt;
                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                &lt;b&gt;As UX designers, we&#39;re practical problem solvers&lt;/b&gt;. For us it&#39;s more about the functionality; there&#39;s no such thing as a proper way. You can&#39;t really &quot;fake&quot; a natural language demo, but there are still more and less practical ways of achieving your goal. What I learned in the process was that &lt;i&gt; even though &lt;/i&gt; we have these new techniques like deep learning at our hands, the agent/program doesn&#39;t have to think the same way a human does in order to present itself like it thinks the same way a human does.
                &lt;p&gt;

                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                &lt;b&gt;There&#39;s nothing wrong with artificial intelligence being artificial&lt;/b&gt;. And we ourselves rely on this phenomenon all the time - like when you interview, or when your when someone asks you for advice (kidding). Realizing this was a milestone in my jedi journey as a designer that codes (basically coding = the dark side; solving abstract problems becomes tempting as your powers grow but designers maintain order by using our judgement aka the force to create things people actually care about).
                &lt;p&gt; 

                &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Related projects&lt;/h1&gt;
                &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
                &lt;b&gt;Each year some work from our studio is shown publicly at CES&lt;/b&gt;. If you want to get a better idea of how intelligent interaction plays into cars, check out these projects my team has worked on in the past. Just to be clear, I was not involved in either of these past projects.
                &lt;p&gt;

                  &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;2015 F 015&lt;/h1&gt;
                  
                  &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/GAz42C5Vvt8&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                   &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;2016 concept IAA&lt;/h1&gt;
                 
                  &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fBwmH7TAupI&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

        

      
    
  
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Mercedes/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Mercedes/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Airquail</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
        



        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; &lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;i&gt; Airquail is the internet of things hardware startup that I cofounded. It started as a weekend hackathon project, and for 12 weeks it turned into a fulltime pursuit after we joined the Hackcelerator accelerator program. We&#39;re currently on our 3rd hardware prototype and have our devices in local school districts. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Story&lt;/h1&gt;

        &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Nu4WogMWovU?start=1160&amp;amp;end=1219&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Sorry if I was a little nervous...there were 140 investors in the crowd&lt;/p&gt;


        
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Part 1: hardware product design&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/wtf.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
        Our time and resources are limited, so we made some tough decisions on which combinations of gases we wanted to monitor. Early on, when making decisions about the product, it&#39;s not always about the customer, the market, or what&#39;s usable. If we were going to dedicate our lives to building a product, it better be something we ourselves wanted to use. So although healthcare was a hot market, I strongly believed we should focus more on gases associated with comfort and wellness. We don&#39;t want to be an alarm that monitors that monitors that toxic gas that will kills 50 people a year, and we also didn&#39;t want to just monitor gases that will shorten your lives by 12 months. Instead, it&#39;s about telling people more about the gases that are always around you yet you can&#39;t see and how they can unconsciously influence your lifestyle. So that&#39;s why we went with Carbon Dioxide, Carbon Monoxide, Pm 2.5. We also added other sensors such as temperature, humidity, pressure for the sole purpose of making our primary gas algorithms more accurate.
        &lt;p&gt;


     &lt;!--    Hardware design
        It had to be portable, why we selected wifi , form factor and costs $90

        Software
        We had an ios app and webapp and showed epa data blablalbalbalal

        Finding partnerships
        How we found chiense company --&gt;

   &lt;!--      &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;The team&lt;/h1&gt; --&gt;
      




        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/ca4.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  For our prototypes, we 3d printed our own enclosures. Small vents allowed for passive air diffusion. This worked well when the device just sat around to collect gradual changes. For demo purposes and with certain gases requiring faster readings, we learned that sometimes active intake was more ideal.   &lt;p&gt;           

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/h3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
        Unlike competitors, we wanted our device to have (1) better integration with appliances and (2) better integration with user lifestyle. The first step to smart home integration was creating our own REST API that other devices and appliances could read. (After setting up our device at a few schools, we learned that it was very difficult to connect our devices to the different wifi networks found in schools and businesses.) To meet our second goal we needed a portable device that was small enough to carry and powered by a battery. We couldn&#39;t create a device that just plugged into the wall and sat by the nightstand all day. When I was testing our first device, it was so much fun carrying it around and seeing with my own eyes how the gases in my environment would change wherever I went. 
        &lt;p&gt;
        

        

        
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Part 2: software product design&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
        Our first webapp was just a proof of concept. We started by pulling data from the EPA to compare with the data from our own device. By typing a zipcode, you could see some general readings from public weather stations regarding dust and carbon monoxide levels. &lt;/p&gt;


        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/app3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
        After refining our technology, we needed to build a more serious backend supporting more users - it also didn&#39;t hurt to give the layout a facelift. We added multi user and device support, more historical data, more gas sensors, and new charts using c3.js. We also had an iOS app in test flight that we killed, so we made our webapp more usable on a mobile browsers. &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/dd1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Part 3: the service&lt;/h1&gt;
         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Demonstrating increased health hazard around heavy traffic &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/ss1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Demonstrating the sensitivity of our device: &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/airquail/ss3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        

 
       
        


      
    
  

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/AirQuail/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/AirQuail/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Fedup&lt;/h1&gt;



        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;It&#39;s crazy that in the 21st century law enforcement/legal system still rely heavily on foggy testimony and paper police reports. So we built a complete ecosystem for users to directly document, review and share evidence without having to go through anyone else. &lt;/p&gt;

         &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
          &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xdvQbL0FFj8&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
         &lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Design considerations&lt;/h1&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Visually, the goal was to make the android app look like a badge worn by an officer - it goes along with our mission making citizens feel more empowered. &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/fedup/a1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;



        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  At the same time, we wanted to protect user privacy and allow them to run the app from their pocket. For this reason, we went recording audio instead of recording Video. Video would have also made our technology less usable in conditions with poor lighting.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Unlike our android app, the web component carried a lighter layout intended for use on the desktop. Whether it&#39;s the victim organizing an account the day after, lawyers browsing client folders, or public viewers browsing fact-oriented stories, the key was to deisgn a pleasant layout that supports a wide variety of media without dumbing content down. &lt;p&gt;




          &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Update&lt;/h1&gt;

          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/fedup/banner.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;



          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; After deciding to continue this project, we connected with the American Civil Liberties Union and entered an official partnership with them. We also connected with the Harvard Law&#39;s Berkman Center. The goal of working with these larger organizations was gain access to more data for our web component.&lt;/p&gt;

        

      
    
  
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2007 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Fed-Up/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Fed-Up/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; &lt;/h1&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;i&gt; Over the summer, I went to Chimehack2 with a few friends. It was a hackathon hosted by Twitter to promote hacking for change. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

      




      &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Making College a Safer Space&lt;/h1&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; A key theme at Chimehack was campus safety. It was an issue my teammates and I had all recently witnessed in college, so from the start it was clear this was the problem we wanted to spend our weekend solving. While brainstorming, we thought back on our experiences involving campus safety. &lt;p&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
      Usually when your friend goes missing, they&#39;re not picking up their phone and you don&#39;t know whether or not their phone is dead. They&#39;re probably not in enough danger to call campus safety, but that doesn&#39;t mean you&#39;re not concerned for your friend. &lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; That&#39;s why we built an iOS app called asOne. It&#39;s a better way to communicate in groups when going out. Instead of annoying group messages, we create temporary friend groups that shares information about each member&#39;s location, battery level, and the time they want to go home. &lt;/p&gt;


      &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;An entire iOS app in 48 hours&lt;/h1&gt;   
       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/asone/asonef.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Because we had 48 hours to build everything, I had about 12 hours to work through the user flow and freeze visual design. We formed teams friday night. I spent the next morning designing and going through tough choices with my teammates, and exported the assets a little after lunch. What follows is a run through some choices I made.&lt;/p&gt;

     

       &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Onboarding and privacy concerns&lt;/h1&gt;   

      &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Usability and the onboarding process was a key concern for me. Nobody was going to use our app, and nobody was going to use our app when they really needed to, if it was hard to sign up, log in, and begin seeing the value we provide. Because we were at twitter, we received a lot of feedback about the challenges when creating a product that only works when many users choose to engage. &lt;p&gt;

         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; With that in mind, it became clear to me that we weren&#39;t here to build a social media app. Having a social network was only the means to our goal. The only thing we came here to do was make it easier for college students to look after their friends. We didn&#39;t need to create our own user id system, we can just use the facebook SDK. The main drawback to this solution was issues of privacy. Our remedy was a system where the group you formed only lasts until the next morning; to use the app again, you must reform a group. To minimize friction in this process, we included recent and nearby friends at the top.&lt;p&gt;

         &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Style&lt;/h1&gt;   
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/asone/a6.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Inclusiveness was a major theme throughout both Chimehack and the mission our technology. To convey this sense of passion and inclusion, I went with an intertwined heart with warm blends. Another goal of mine was to make something useful for a diverse demographic - not just urban techies surfing producthunt. One effort to make sure we didn&#39;t attract the traditional SF user base was to make the app look less stereotypical, hence the granjon/roman typeface that you may recognise when walking around a mall...&lt;/p&gt;   


       
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Resting view&lt;/h1&gt;   
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/asone/a1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  The resting screen makes it easy to check up on your friends periodically. When designing this view, I thought back to all the things I can&#39;t do just by calling each individual in my group. 

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;

          1. Assuming my friends pick up, I probably won&#39;t be able to hear them speak well, so the first thing I want is an easy way to get exactly a status update. &lt;p&gt;

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
          
          2. An easy way to glance over all my group members at once so I don&#39;t have to call each of them individually. &lt;p&gt;

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;

          3. They&#39;re probably not all going to pickup anyways, so I&#39;d rather just look at where they are on a map. &lt;p&gt;

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;

          4. If I can&#39;t look at where they are that means their battery is probably dead - so I want to be able to see what their battery status is.&lt;p&gt;

        &lt;/p&gt;   


        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Details view&lt;/h1&gt;  
        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/asone/a5.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Usually when everyone&#39;s ready to go home, there&#39;s that one person that nobody can find. So we created a detail view as an extension to the group view. Tapping on your friend brings you to more actions such as sending a push notification and enabling audio. Additionally we automatically set the true north of the inline map to that of the friend. &lt;/p&gt;
       &lt;!--  &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot;  src=&quot;../../images/asone.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; &gt;    --&gt;


        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; We built this app because this was a tool missing from our everyday lives, and for the rest of the summer we would often use it as a tool to ping and find eachother. Since then, Apple released a standalone friend finder, and we also saw an app named Companion gain popularity around college campuses. &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; In retrospect, the technology wasn&#39;t earth shattering, but this is a great example of how fast a talented team can work decisively when there is good chemistry. In one weekend, we shipped a product that would take a company at least half a year to assemble.&lt;/p&gt;

        
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;More about Chimehack&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
        &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/86ECVBcPWcg&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
        

        
      
    
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2006 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/As-One/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/As-One/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Benzpay</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; &lt;/h1&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;i&gt; This is the winning hackathon project that caught the attention of Daimler&#39;s board members. We had the chance to meet Dr. Z as well as all the other executives during their yearly meeting. They were extremely impressed, and subsequently what lead me to a job at Mercedes. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Simplifying the driving experience &lt;/h1&gt;

         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Lots of technology we take for granted on our phones are not utilized in cars. Mobile payment, for instance, is all around us. It&#39;s made our lives easier and more secure. Yet when leaving a parking garage or stopping at a toll booth, we still waste time and fumble to make a transaction.  &lt;p&gt;

          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/benzpay.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

           &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
          We&#39;re not getting from point A to point B in the most efficient way possible. That&#39;s why we created BenzPay, because for the Mercedes driver, time is the only currency that matters.  &lt;/p&gt;

         &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Boiling down the use case &lt;/h1&gt;
         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  For our short demo, we paired down the concept to three distinct use cases. Speaking to drivers and industry experts, it became clear gas and parking were most popular. However there was no clear contender for the third use case, making it a harder decision. &lt;p&gt;

          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/a3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
          Not everyone was a fan of going with &quot;events&quot; instead of &quot;tollbooth&quot; but here is my reasoning:

          &lt;ol type=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Payment sollutions for tollbooths already exist &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;I want to appeal to the emotional side of our product. It&#39;s one thing to make your life easier, it&#39;s another to make it more interesting.  &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Quick to implement, completing transactions on ticketmaster or eventbrite requires no additional hardware or data collection - unlike support for parking meters, gas pumps, or toll booths. &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;/ol&gt;
           &lt;/p&gt;


       

        &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/a4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;


          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
            Additional features include using gps and bitcoin to complete transactions without the need to stop, or by automatically calculating and paying for the price to fill up at a given gas station. 
            &lt;p&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Driver usability: automate transactions &lt;/h1&gt;     

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  
        Designing for the car is different than designing for mobile. Unless the driver is parked, most interactions occur without the user&#39;s complete attention. That&#39;s why we made initiating a transaction automatic. All the driver needs to do is confirm the amount alerted to the driver. Bitcoin was the easiest to integrate for our prototype, but we soon discovered the security benefits of using bitcoin.

       
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Driver usability: mapping input interaction &lt;/h1&gt;    
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  
        A common gripe from c300 owners is that the heads-up display looks like it&#39;s touchscreen but it really isn&#39;t. To avoid this confusion and make event handling more intuitive, I created an interface with a clear hierarchy of menus naviated through a selector. &lt;p&gt;

          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/a6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;


         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
        Rotating the wheel makes the selector scroll up, down, in and out of the menus depending on the context of the selector. Shifting the wheel left and right toggles different views like &quot;payment history,&quot; &quot;payment preferences,&quot; and &quot;nearby transactions.&quot;
        &lt;p&gt;


          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/g.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;
       

      

         &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Driver usability: glanceable interface &lt;/h1&gt;         
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  
        I used a variation of color, size, and weight to distinguish what really matters at a glance from information important only on a closer read. 
        &lt;p&gt;

            &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/a5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

              &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  
                An example of this can be seen in the payment history view. The first thing the driver sees is the amount paid followed by the vendor name. Details such as credit card number and bitcoin address is more confidential and signifigantly less visible from a distance.  &lt;p&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Demo video &lt;/h1&gt;  

         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crunchbase.com/person/yashad-kulkarni#/entity&quot;&gt; Yashad from TechCrunch &lt;/a&gt;filmed this video for us.

           &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/132971331&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Further reading &lt;/h1&gt;  

           
            &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/benzpay/team.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

              &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mobilegeeks.com/mercedes-benz-hack-a-thon-a-snapshot-of-developing-for-automotive/&quot;&gt; Writeup by Mobile Geeks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;

           &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://360.here.com/2015/08/11/here-gives-direction-at-mercedes-benz-hackathon/&quot;&gt; Article by HERE maps &lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;


          

            
                 

         


      
    
  

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/BenzPay/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/BenzPay/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left &quot;&gt;



      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;


             &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; &lt;/h1&gt;
            &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; &lt;i&gt; People who are really serious about software should make their own hardware. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;Wifi Beerbong&lt;/h1&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; I showed up to Mhacks 6 with a giant briefcase of hardware. It&#39;s really important for me to make things other people haven&#39;t, so whenever I find a novel gadget or sensor, I toss it in my hardware collection. &lt;p&gt;

          &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/beerbong/kit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
            I figured it would be fun to fly in a couple days early. It was the first week of classes and I had a couple of friends at the University of Michigan that I wanted to visit. Long story short, there was a block party, a bunch of people were standing on top of my friend&#39;s table and it snapped. &lt;p&gt;

             &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/beerbong/classic.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

            &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
            While looking for screws the next day at the hardware store, I come across something you would only see in Ann Arbor.....In the gardening section there was an entire aisle dedicated to beer bong funnels, hoses, and accesories. At that point, it became very clear to me that for Mhacks 6 I was going to make the world&#39;s first wifi enabled beer bong. &lt;p&gt;


         

          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/drankadank&quot;&gt; https://github.com/drankadank &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;

              &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;The world&#39;s first wifi enabled beerbong&lt;/h1&gt;


         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Clearly this wasn&#39;t going to be a 1-device-1-user sort of thing, more likely 1-device-1-friend group. A single device had to support multiple users, so it made sense to have a log in feature that integrated well with social media.   &lt;/p&gt;

           &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/beerbong/f1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;



         &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; The annoying thing with Particle (link) photons is that they run off 3.3v and a lot of sensors run off 5v. Since we were powering the photon with a usb battery pack, the original plan was to use that power with a voltage divider. I&#39;m not an electrical engineer, but i just decided to just tap into the VIN of the photon. People were telling me not to do that, but it&#39;s been working as long as I make sure the ground is not floating around.  &lt;/p&gt;


       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/beerbong/circuit2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; The only resistors I ended up needing were for the led indicators.   &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/beerbong/userfloww.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;






        
      
    
  

&lt;!--   &lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;row text-center&quot;&gt;
   &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;tagline&quot;&gt; 
      
         
          &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; 
         We short circuited everything on our first test. Luckily I had a seconded particle photon with me. Made sure our enclosure was waterproof.
        &lt;/p&gt;

           &lt;img class=&quot;content-image-vertical&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/beerbong/a1.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; &gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Wifi-Beerbong/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Wifi-Beerbong/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
       &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;1972 Firebird&lt;/h1&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Basically, when I was a freshmen in college, I bought a muscle car with holes in the floor and worms in the seats. &lt;/p&gt;


       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; I rebuilt the motor in my dorm parking lot. Me retapping an engine block thread: &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; My hallmates complained it always smelled like gasoline &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Hey at least I didn&#39;t set the place on fire &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; I also rewired all the electronics &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; And made my own dashboard out of pine &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;

       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; I usually drive it around without the hood &lt;/p&gt;

       &lt;img class=&quot;content-image&quot; src=&quot;../../images/projects/firebird/r6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeff&quot; /&gt;


       &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; So yeah I like cars &lt;/p&gt;

     &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2003 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Firebird/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Firebird/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Music Videos &lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Back in college, I used to work in video production and post-production. Here are a few videos from work/fun. They&#39;ve been featured on some of those hip underground sites.&lt;/p&gt;

        

            

              &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; On the steps &lt;/h1&gt;
              &lt;!-- &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; My favorite part about rappers is their work ethic - the hustle, the grind - having a dayjob and hitting the studio at night. I guess it&#39;s the same reason I love startups. It&#39;s about being young, living your dreams while everyones telling you your stupid. &lt;/p&gt; --&gt;

               &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;  Visually I wanted to extend the mood of the song. The shutter speed is slow to get that smooth motion blur, and the cuts are also slow. Shot at 35mm and 50mm wide open so its tight but soft. Didn&#39;t want to overdo camera movement, so  I kept things interesting with carefully planned sequenced lighting. I preserved the beautiful characteristics and colors from dim ambient light while adding very subtle reflected accents through sources such as my warm car blinkers or my cool phone flash covered by my finger.
                &lt;/p&gt;

               &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                  &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JkA_sGRfyKA&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
               &lt;/div&gt;


              &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; SOS &lt;/h1&gt;
              &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; This one of those day in the life college music videos. Most rap videos in recent years are shot on cropped sensors with tight lenses, resulting in a lot of camera shake remedied by fast cuts - it&#39;s a nice raw style. But this video looks different because many shots are of a much wider angle. The intro is way too long, and for the 10k views we got, half of them probably stopped watching it before the video even started. &lt;/p&gt;



               &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                  &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/1zxIuoUDaXA&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
               &lt;/div&gt;



               &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt; Salad Days &lt;/h1&gt;
              &lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt; Pickathon is Portland&#39;s largest music festival. Like everything in Portland, it&#39;s super underground and happens in a forest.&lt;/p&gt;

               &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
                  &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VoGNw78eYzc&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
               &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2002 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Music-Videos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/Music-Videos/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> </title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left&quot;&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h1 class=&quot;title-main-about&quot;&gt;  &lt;/h1&gt;


        &lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt; 
            &lt;div class=&quot;row text-left buffer0&quot;&gt;



              

              &lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/users/33963267&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
              



&lt;!-- 
           &lt;embed class=&quot;resume&quot; src=&quot;../../images/rresume.pdf&quot; alt=&quot;pdf viewer only&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500px&quot; alt=&quot;pdf&quot; pluginspage=&quot;http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep2.html&quot;&gt;

              &lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-4by3&quot;&gt;
                  &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;../../images/rresume.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
 --&gt;

		
            &lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/project-item/More-Projects/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/project-item/More-Projects/</guid>
        
        
        <category>project-item</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
